BARDHI GRAINCA

DevOps Engineer

bardhi.grainca@hotmail.com

+389 76 466 033

About

I am an operations engineer with 2.5 years of experience in DevOps infrastructure and 4 years in Design. My strong culture for enterprise DevOps teams has been engraved in my daily life and is part of me. I also have 5 years of solid experience in direct sales where I acquired my communication skills with different clients. I have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and have a multiple certificate in leadership. My passion is design and in my spare time I take smaller projects for fun.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2017

South East European University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Experience

SEAVUS (Sunrise Swiss Telecom)

Mar 2018 - Jan 2019

IT and Operations Engineer

Part of Sunrise Swiss Telecom project. Provide assistance concerning the use of computer hardware and software, including operating systems and application, databases, network, security. Execute operational activities following schedule of activities and independent monitors, the performance of the system. Responsible for the technical IT system operations or databases LDAP, MySQL, TOAD, SOAP, Active Directories. Incident Management, Documentation and problem-solving initiatives.

SEAVUS

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

Tech Support Specialist

Diagnosing and solving customer problems/requests or software issues and provide technical assistance to the costumer. Test and reproduce reported issues and answer the technical questions, resolve customer problems. Execute operation activities following schedule of daily

activities. Monitor performance of the systems and other relevant activities related to this position. First- and Second-line support.

Stopanska Banka Main Branch

Mar 2019 - Nov 2019

System Analyst

I was part of a web application development cycle. Where employees of Stopanska can see a client's status and credit background when applying for loans. I've gained a lot of experience regarding banking systems, financing and tax regulations. It is a successful application that is live and in use.

Singular

Nov 2019 – Present

DevOps

Continuous integration (CI) continuous delivery (CD) with Jenkins, Monitoring with Grafana (Percona), PRTG, Prometheus (Alertmanager), Troubleshooting application bugs, Database management (MySql), Log management (Graylog), Jira incident management ticketing, Bash Scripting, Automation, AWS, AZURE, Docker, Kubernetes

Freelance

Jan 2015 – Present

In my spare time I find smaller projects to do I have solid experience in Brand identity and design, web design, I also have managed 3 bigger projects for companies from United States. Please refer to the links below to see the websites:

http://www.nyallran.com/ USA, NYC

http://fahrenheit-nyc.com/ USA, NYC

http://realrok.com/ USA, NYC

Skills

- Incident Management, MySQL, SOAP, TOAD, LDAP, APACHE, IMS, .NET, SAP.
- Customer Service 1nd Level, 2nd Level, Windows Server 14, 16
- Network Administrator, Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Identity Management NetIQ, Work with clients 1 on 1
- Prototyping in XD, PSD, AI and converting them into Functional Web pages.
- HTML/CSS/Java Script, jQuery, UX/UI, Bootstrap
- Adobe Ps, Ai, XD, Id, Ae

Languages

Native: Albanian

Fluent: English, Macedonian

Certificates

2015

We Can Code

Full one day workshop, first place for best web page.

2015

Global Leaders

Communication skills, leadership,

network building, organization and public speeches.

Duration 7 days.